Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series I: Books Illustrated and/or Authored by Leonard Everett Fisher ,undated, 1927-1999
  - Colonial Craftsmen Series II
    - The Blacksmiths, 1976
      - Manuscript, page 7, undated (Box 9:369)
      - Manuscript, page 8, undated (Box 9:370)
      - Manuscript, page 9, undated (Box 9:371)
      - Manuscript, page 10, undated (Box 9:372)
      - Manuscript, page 11, undated (Box 9:373)
      - Title page, 1976 (Box 9:374)
    - The Printers, 1965
      - Book plan, undated (Box 9:375)
      - Draft / notes, undated (Box 9:376)
      - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 9:377)
  - Ellis Island, 1986
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 10:378A)
    - Early drafts (scrap), undated (Box 10:378)
    - Manuscript, 1985 (Box 10:379)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 10:380A)
    - Manuscript, 1985 November 6 (Box 10:380)
    - Manuscript with typesetter's instructions, undated (Box 10:381)
    - Photo caption of manuscript and proof, undated (Box 10:382)
    - Master Proof, 1985 December 20 (Box 10:383)
    - Author's proof, 1985 December 20 (Box 10:384)
    - Galley proof (photocopy), undated (Box 10:385)
    - Index, proof, undated (Box 10:386)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 10:387)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 10:388A)
  - The Seven Days of Creation, 1981
    - Book Plan, undated (Box 10:388)
    - Draft, Notes, undated (Box 10:389)
    - Manuscript, 1980 July 25 (Box 10:390)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 10:391)
    - Manuscript (editor's comments), undated (Box 10:392)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 10:393)
    - Manuscript, 1980 August 4 (Box 10:394)
    - Manuscript, 1980 August 14 (Box 10:395)
    - Manuscript, 1980 August 18 (Box 10:396)
    - Manuscript, 1980 November 29 (Box 10:397)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 10:398)
    - Specification sheet, undated (Box 10:399)
    - Text, undated (Box 10:400)
    - Proof (photocopy), 1981 April 5 (Box 10:401)
    - Proof (photocopy), undated (Box 10:402)
    - Press proof (incomplete), undated (Box 10:403)
    - Acrylic illustrations (12), 1981 (Box 53:1463)
  - 
    - Notes, undated (Box 11:404)
    - Book plan, undated (Box 11:405)
    - Letter, expert opinion, undated (Box 11:406)
    - Printer notes, undated (Box 11:407)
    - Character letter drawings, undated (Box 11:408)
    - Characters, computer printout, undated (Box 11:409)
    - Characters, letters, photocopies, undated (Box 11:410)
    - Galley proof, undated (Box 11:411)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 11:412)
    - Press proof (uncut), undated (Box 11:413)
    - Proposal for sequel to Alphabet Art, 1978 (Box 11:414)
  - Calendar Art, 1987
    - Notes, undated (Box 11:415)
    - Proposal, undated (Box 11:416)
    - Outlin, undated (Box 11:417)
    - Manuscript (copy edited), undated (Box 11:418)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 11:419)
    - Manuscript (photocopy), undated (Box 11:420)
    - Galley proof, 1987 (Box 11:421)
    - Dust jacket, press proof, undated (Box 11:422)
    - Dust jacket, undated (Box 11:423)
    - Galley proof, undated (Box 11:424)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11:425)
    - Jacket, undated (Box 23:744)
  - The Olympians, 1984
    - Notes, undated (Box 12:426)
    - Manuscript (edited), undated (Box 12:427)
    - Manuscript (type setting instructions), undated (Box 12:428)
    - Master proof, undated (Box 12:429)
    - Proof (photocopy), undated (Box 12:430)
    - Proof (photocopy), 1984 March 8 (Box 12:431)
    - Preliminary illustrations, undated (Box 12:432)
    - Uncut press proof, undated (Box 12:433)
    - Press proof, undated (Box 12:434)
    - Dust jacket & Press proof, undated (Box 12:435)
  - Star Signs, 1983
    - Book plans, notes & early artwork, undated (Box 12:436)
    - Manuscript, 1982 November 30 (Box 12:437)
    - Manuscript (edited), undated (Box 12:438)
    - Early dummy, undated (Box 12:439)
    - Text sample, undated (Box 12:440)
    - Mechanical directions, undated (Box 12:441)
    - Author's proof, undated (Box 12:442)
    - Proof paste-ups, undated (Box 12:443)
    - Art work, undated (Box 12:444)
    - Book mock-up (using text from galley proof), undated (Box 12:445)
    - Book jacket specifications, undated (Box 12:446)
    - Flap detail, undated (Box 12:447)
    - Press proofs (edited), undated (Box 12:448)
    - Uncut press proofs, undated (Box 12:449)
    - Press proof, undated (Box 12:450)
    - Miscellaneous press proofs, undated (Box 12:451)
    - Correspondence, 1983 September 20 (Box 12:452)
  - The White House, 1989
    - Notes & Research, undated (Box 13:453)
    - Bibliography for research, undated (Box 13:454)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 13:455)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 13:456)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 13:457)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 13:458)
    - Manuscript with copy editor's comments, undated (Box 13:459)
    - Index with copy editor's comments, 1989 June 2 (Box 13:460)
    - Copy-editing comments, undated (Box 13:461)
    - Proof, 1989 January 24 (Box 13:462)
    - Proof, 1989 January 24 (Box 13:463)
    - Proof, 1989 April 17 (Box 13:464)
    - Proof, 1989 April 17 (Box 13:465)
    - Proof, 1989 May 18 (Box 13:466)
    - Proof, 1989 May 19 (Box 13:467)
    - Proof, 1989 June 9 (Box 13:468)
    - Proof, index, 1989 June 16 (Box 13:469)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 13:470)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 13:471)
    - List of illustrations, undated (Box 13:472)
    - Illustration, White House floor plan, undated (Box 13:473)
    - Illustration: Acrylic, "Leinster House", "Rastignac", 1989 May 5 (Box 13:474)
    - Illustration: Acrylic, "Russel Hoban", 1989 May 5 (Box 13:475)
    - Photo negative, "The White House", undated (Box 13:476)
    - Photo, "North Front Portico", undated (Box 13:477)
    - Photo, "Main Entrance North Front", undated (Box 13:478)
    - Photo, "South Portico 1952", undated (Box 13:479)
    - Photo, "Quentin Roosevelt on Algonquin 1902 June 17", undated (Box 13:480)
    - Photo, "Police Role Call 1902", undated (Box 13:481)
    - Photo, "L'Enfant's Plan of Washington D.C. 1791", undated (Box 13:482)
    - Photo, "Jefferson's Design for White House 1792", undated (Box 13:483)
    - Photo, "Original Design by Russel Hoban 1792", undated (Box 13:484)
    - Photo, "Diplomatic Reception Room 1961", undated (Box 13:485)
    - Photo, "The Oval Office", undated (Box 13:486)
    - Photo, "George Washington" by Gilbert Stuart 1797", undated (Box 13:487)
    - Photo, "Dolly Payne Madison 1848" by William Ellwell, undated (Box 13:488)
    - Photo, "Drawing of President's House 1821", undated (Box 13:489)
    - Photo, "North Front Portico c.1948", undated (Box 13:490)
    - Photo, "South Portico c.1948", undated (Box 13:491)
    - Photo, "Lincoln", undated (Box 13:492)
    - Photo, "White House c.1861", undated (Box 13:493)
    - Photo, "Lincoln's Bedroom", undated (Box 13:494)
    - Photo, "Colored Servants at the White House 1877", undated (Box 13:495)
    - Photo, "The Tiffany Screens 1883", undated (Box 13:496)
    - Photo, "Harrison's Office 1889", undated (Box 13:497)
    - Photo, "The Conservatory 1889", undated (Box 13:498)
    - Photo, "The Harrison's c.1890", undated (Box 13:499)
    - Photo, "Green Room and Mrs. Hayes 1893", undated (Box 13:500)
    - Photo, "Red Room and the Hayes 1893-1902", undated (Box 13:501)
    - Photo, "East Room 1893", undated (Box 13:502)
    - Photo, "Blue Room 1899", undated (Box 13:503)
    - Photo, "State Dining Room 1900", undated (Box 13:504)
    - Photo, "Guard House c.1900", undated (Box 13:505)
    - Photo, "East Front 1909", undated (Box 13:506)
    - Photo, "Office Building and Tennis-Court 1909", undated (Box 13:507)
    - Photo, "Kitchen 1901", undated (Box 13:508)
    - Photo, "South Portico, Wilbur Wright in Flight 1911", undated (Box 13:509)
    - Photo, "Sheep on South Lawn 1919", undated (Box 13:510)
    - Photo, "Easter Egg Role on South Lawn 1921", undated (Box 13:511)
    - Photo, "Fire in Executive Office Building 1914", undated (Box 13:512)
    - Photo, "The F.D.R. Roosevelts", undated (Box 13:513)
    - Photo, "Reagan's Desk c.1980", undated (Box 13:514)
    - Photo, "North Front 1941", undated (Box 13:515)
    - Photo, "Truman and Margaret Ann Ford 1945", undated (Box 13:516)
    - Photo, "Gutted Interior 1948", undated (Box 13:517)
    - Photo, "Jacqueline Kennedy 1962", undated (Box 13:518)
    - Photo, "Treaty Room 1961", undated (Box 13:519)
    - Photo, "John F. Kennedy and Pablo Casals 1961", undated (Box 13:520)
    - Photo, "John F. Kennedy and John Junior 1963", undated (Box 13:521)
    - Photo, "Pat Nixon", undated (Box 13:522)
    - Photo, "President and Mrs. Reagan 1987", undated (Box 13:523)
    - Photo, "South-East View of White House c.1948", undated (Box 13:524)
    - Photo, "North-West View of White House", undated (Box 13:525)
    - Photo, "Booker T. Washington 1859", undated (Box 13:526)
    - Photo, "Abraham Lincoln 1863", undated (Box 13:527)
    - Photo, "Lincoln", undated (Box 13:528)
    - Photo, "Blue Room c.1899", undated (Box 13:529)
    - Photo, " Oval Office (after Dec. 24, 1929 fire) c. 1930", undated (Box 13:530)
    - Photo, "Cabinet Room 1889", undated (Box 13:531)
    - Photo, "Grover Cleveland c.1893", undated (Box 13:532)
    - Photo, "1911 Public Reception", undated (Box 13:533)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 13:534)
    - Letter to President and Mrs. Bush, 1989 November 6 (Box 13:535)
  - The ABC Exhibit, 1991
    - Notes, undated (Box 14:536)
    - Book plan, undated (Box 14:537)
    - Early book outline, undated (Box 14:538)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:539)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:540)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:541)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:542)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:543)
    - Title page, undated (Box 14:544)
    - Guitar drawing, undated (Box 14:545)
    - Dummy, 1990 June 4 (Box 14:546)
    - Flap text, undated (Box 14:547)
    - Proof, undated (Box 14:548)
    - Cut press proof, undated (Box 14:549)
    - Promotional poster, undated (Box 14:550)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 14:551)
    - Duplicate film, undated (Box 14:552)
  - Niagara Falls, 1996
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:553)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:554)
    - Manuscript (index), undated (Box 14:555)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 14:556)
    - Printer's instructions, undated (Box 14:557)
    - Galley proof, 1995 August 22 (Box 14:558)
    - Proof, 1995 August 22 (Box 14:559)
    - Galley proofs, 1995 December 27 (Box 14:560)
    - Galley proofs, 1996 February (Box 14:561)
    - Photographs and negatives, undated (Box 14:562)
    - Proof, photo and map text, undated (Box 14:563)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 14:564)
    - Proof, flap and jacket text, undated (Box 14:565)
    - Proof (index), undated (Box 14:566)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 14:567)
  - Number Art, 1982
    - Research and Notes, undated (Box 15:568)
    - Book plan, undated (Box 15:569)
    - Bibliography, undated (Box 15:570)
    - Manuscript (edited), undated (Box 15:571)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 15:572)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 15:573)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 15:574)
    - Photocopy of artwork, undated (Box 15:575)
    - Artwork proofs, undated (Box 15:576)
    - Text sample, undated (Box 15:577)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 15:578)
  - Symbol Art, 1985
    - Book plan, undated (Box 15:579)
    - Notes, undated (Box 15:580A)
    - Symbols- miscellaneous, undated (Box 15:580B)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 15:580)
    - Manuscript (copy), undated (Box 15:581)
    - Artwork draft, undated (Box 15:582)
    - Galley proof, undated (Box 15:583)
    - Book-incomplete, undated (Box 15:584)
    - Correspondence Re: Logos to be included, 1985 (Box 15:585A)
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 15:585)
    - Cover illustration, scratchboard, undated (Box 23:743)
  - Boxes! Boxes!, 1984
    - Author's correspondence with author, undated (Box 16:586)
    - Illustration notes, undated (Box 16:587A)
    - Manuscript / Book plans, undated (Box 16:587)
    - About the book, undated (Box 16:588)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 16:589)
    - Illustrations, undated (Box 16:590)
    - Rough illustrations, undated (Box 16:591)
    - Proof, undated (Box 16:591A)
    - Book jacket and dimensions, undated (Box 16:592)
  - Jason and the Golden Fleece, 1990
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 16:593)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 16:594)
    - Manuscript, 1989 April 10 (Box 16:595)
    - Manuscript (edited) and editor's correspondence, undated (Box 16:596)
    - Manuscript, 1989 May 6 (Box 16:597)
    - Manuscript (edited), undated (Box 16:598)
    - Proof, undated (Box 16:599)
    - Proof, undated (Box 16:600)
    - Proof, undated (Box 16:601)
    - Book plan, undated (Box 16:602)
    - Galley proof, undated (Box 16:603)
    - F & G manuscript, undated (Box 16:604)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 16:605)
  - Stars & Stripes, 1993
    - New York Times clippings, 1992 December 6 (Box 16:606)
    - Research, undated (Box 16:607)
    - Book plan, early illustrations, undated (Box 16:608)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 16:609)
    - Manuscript draft, undated (Box 16:610)
    - Manuscript (edited), 1992 November 11 (Box 16:611)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 16:612)
    - Manuscript with typesetting directions, undated (Box 16:613)
    - Jacket text with typesetting directions, undated (Box 16:614)
    - Miscellaneous typesetting / printing instructions, undated (Box 16:615)
    - Dummy, undated (Box 16:616)
    - Proof, 1993 February 18 (Box 16:617)
    - Proof, 1993 January 23 (Box 16:618)
    - Dummy draft, undated (Box 16:619)
    - Dummy draft, undated (Box 16:620)
    - Dummy draft, revised, 1992 December 1 (Box 16:621)
    - Press proof (cut), undated (Box 16:622)
    - Press proof (cut), undated (Box 16:623)
    - Press proof (uncut), undated (Box 16:624)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 16:625)
  - Two if by Sea, 1970
    - Notes, introduction, book plan, undated (Box 17:626)
    - Book outline / proposal, undated (Box 17:627)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:628)
    - Manuscript, self edited, undated (Box 17:629)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:630)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:631)
    - Manuscript, introduction and prologue, undated (Box 17:632)
    - Manuscript, "General Gage", undated (Box 17:633)
    - Manuscript, "General Gage", undated (Box 17:634)
    - Manuscript, "General Gage", undated (Box 17:635)
    - Manuscript, "Dr. John Warren", undated (Box 17:636)
    - Manuscript, "Dr. Warren", undated (Box 17:637)
    - Manuscript, "Mr. Paul Revere", undated (Box 17:638)
    - Manuscript, "Sexton Robert Newman", undated (Box 17:639)
    - Manuscript, "Epilogue", undated (Box 17:640)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:641)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:642)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:643)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:644)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 17:645)
    - Manuscript (edited), undated (Box 17:646)
    - Frontis text, undated (Box 17:647)
    - Cover art, undated (Box 17:648)
    - Illustrations, pencil, undated (Box 17:649)
    - Cover, photo proof specifications, undated (Box 17:650)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 17:651)
    - Musical drama, (notes), undated (Box 17:652)
    - Musical drama, "The Night of the Lanterns", 1970 (Box 17:653)
    - Musical drama, "The Night of the Lanterns", 1970 (Box 17:654)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:655)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:656)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:657)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:658)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:659)
    - Musical drama, manuscript, undated (Box 17:660)
    - Galley proofs (35 pages), undated (Box 21:696)
    - Proofs (roughs), undated (Box 21:697)
    - Proof, undated (Box 21:698)
  - Anasazi, 1996
    - Book proposal #1 and 2, 1995 March, November (Box 18A:660A)
    - Notes, Timelines and maps, undated (Box 18A:660B)
    - Page drafts (with editing), undated (Box 18A:660C)
    - Incomplete manuscript draft, undated (Box 18A:660D)
    - Complete manuscript draft #1, undated (Box 18A:660E)
    - Complete manuscript draft #2, undated (Box 18A:660F)
    - Complete manuscript draft #3 with title pages, undated (Box 18A:660G)
    - Complete manuscript draft #4, undated (Box 18A:660H)
    - Comments from Anthropologist to LEF, 1996 April (Box 18A:660I)
    - Final manuscript draft, undated (Box 18A:660J)
    - Book dummies, 1996 (Box 18A:660K)
    - Galleys w/ editor's notes, 1996 June 20 (Box 18A:660L)
    - 2 Jackets, 1996 (Box 18A:660M)
    - 4 Photo overlays, 1996 (Box 18A:660N)
    - Proofs, 1996 September 17 (Box 18A:660O)
    - Correspondence / Fed-Ex Slips, 1996 (Box 18A:660P)
  - The Gods and Goddesses of Ancient Egypt, 1997
    - Notes, undated (Box 18A:661A)
    - Book Lay-out / Outline, undated (Box 18A:661B)
    - Map Research, undated (Box 18A:661C)
    - Map Text (3 pages), undated (Box 18A:661D)
    - Page drafts -some editing, undated (Box 18A:661D)
    - Manuscript -minimal editing, undated (Box 18A:661E)
    - Manuscript (incomplete), undated (Box 18A:661F)
    - Manuscript (17 pages), undated (Box 18A:661G)
    - Editor's comments, undated (Box 18A:661H)
    - Type samples, undated (Box 18A:661I)
    - Photo overlays (3), 1997 (Box 18A:661J)
    - F & G, 1997 January 3 (Box 18A:661K)
    - Faxed Galley page- from editor, 1997 March 27 (Box 18A:661L)
    - Faxed map -from editor, 1997 April 23 (Box 18A:661M)
    - Faxed jacket text- from editor, 1997 May 1 (Box 18A:661N)
    - Correspondence and Fed-Ex slips, undated (Box 18A:661O)
    - (Box 18:666)
    - Photomechanicals, text (pp. 2-18), undated (Box 19:667)
    - (Box 18:668)
    - (Box 18:669)
    - (Box 18:670)
    - Undated proofs, undated (Box 19:671)
    - Proofs, 1996-1997 (Box 19:672)
    - Photomechanicals, illustrations and text (pp.1-32), undated (Box 19:673)
    - Photomechanicals, illustrations and text (5 items), undated (Box 19:674)
    - Photomechanicals, page proofs (10 pages), undated (Box 19:675)
    - Jacket, undated (Box 19:676)
    - Signed poster, undated (Box 19:676A)
  - Alexander Graham Bell, 1999
    - Jacket cover, 1999 (Box 18A:661P)
    - Edited Manuscript, 1998 February (Box 18A:661Q)
    - Text Changes, 1998 March 1 (Box 18A:661R)
    - Edited Galleys, 1998 (Box 18A:661S)
    - Corrected Mechanicals, 1998 November (Box 18A:661T)
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 18A:661U)
  - To Bigotry No Sanction, 1998
    - Notes and Type Samples, undated (Box 18A:662A)
    - Research, undated (Box 18A:662B)
    - Photo information and copies of, undated (Box 18A:662C)
    - 26 Photographs and Negatives of, undated (Box 18A:662D)
    - Manuscript draft #1, 1997 August 28 (Box 18A:662E)
    - Manuscript draft #2, 1997 August 29 (Box 18A:662F)
    - Manuscript draft #3, 1997 September 4 (Box 18A:662G)
    - Faxed complete manuscript #4, 1998 June 30 (Box 18A:662H)
    - Complete manuscript #5, 1998 July (Box 18A:662I)
    - Complete manuscript #5, 1999 (Box 18A:662J)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 18A:662K)
  - Noonan, 1978
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 22:699)
    - Photomechanicals (pp1-128, 3 other items), undated (Box 22:700)
    - Photomechanicals, cover (2 items), undated (Box 22:701)
    - Book cover, undated (Box 22:702)
    - Flyer, undated (Box 22:702A)
  - Moses, 1995
    - Notes, undated (Box 23:703)
    - Lineage notes, undated (Box 23:704)
    - Manuscript, 1994 January 7 (Box 23:705)
    - Manuscript, 1994 January 8 (Box 23:706)
    - Expert's comments on manuscript, 1994 January 9 (Box 23:707)
    - Manuscript, 1994 January 10 (Box 23:708)
    - Manuscript, 1994 January 12 (Box 23:709)
    - Manuscript, 1994 January 25 (Box 23:710)
    - Reference materials, fax, 1994 March 9 (Box 23:711)
    - Manuscript, 1994 March 29 (Box 23:712)
    - Manuscript, 1994 April 29 (Box 23:713)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 23:714)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 23:715)
    - Author/editor correspondence, undated (Box 23:716)
    - Photo overlays-text, undated (Box 23:717)
    - Galley, 1994 June 20 (Box 23:718)
    - Galley, 1994 October 26 (Box 23:719)
    - Text overlay, undated (Box 23:720)
    - Galley proofs, jacket and frontispiece, undated (Box 23:721)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 23:722)
    - Galley proofs, undated (Box 23:723)
    - Galley dummy, undated (Box 23:724)
    - Cover specifications, undated (Box 23:725)
  - Kinderdike, 1994
    - Manuscript,draft, 1991 August 29 (Box 23:726)
    - Manuscript, 1991 August 30 (Box 23:727)
    - Manuscript, 1991 August 30 (Box 23:728)
    - Manuscript, 1991 September 3 (Box 23:729)
    - Manuscript, 1991 September 27 (Box 23:730)
    - Manuscript, 1991 September 27 (Box 23:731)
    - Manuscript, 1991 October 25 (Box 23:732)
    - Manuscript, 1991 October 25 (Box 23:733)
    - Manuscript, 1991 November 5 (Box 23:734)
    - Manuscript, 1993 March (Box 23:735)
    - Photos (6) of paintings, undated (Box 23:736)
    - Photos (8) of production of book, undated (Box 23:737)
    - Flap text, fax, 1993 April 20 (Box 23:738)
    - Photo overlays-text (pp. 1-3, 5-31 odd, 32), undated (Box 23:739)
    - Photocopy of press proof, undated (Box 23:740)
    - Press proof cover, undated (Box 23:741)
    - Correspondence from art editor, undated (Box 23:742)
  - The Liberty Book, 1975
    - Research notes, undated (Box 24:745)
    - Research, drafts, undated (Box 24:746)
    - Illustration sketches, undated (Box 24:746A)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 24:747)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 24:748)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 24:749)
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 24:750)
    - Photo overlays - text (2), undated (Box 24:751)
    - 9 Negatives, undated (Box 24:751A)
    - Photo overlays - text (2), undated (Box 24:752)
    - Photo overlays - text (3), undated (Box 24:753)
    - Photo overlays - text and music (3), undated (Box 24:754)
    - Photo overlays - text and art work (3), undated (Box 24:755)
    - Photo overlays - text and art work (3), undated (Box 24:756)
    - Scratchboard paste-up, 1974 (Box 24:756A)
    - Scratchboard paste-up, pp. 28/29, 1974 (Box 24:756B)
    - Jacket text, undated (Box 24:757)
    - Photomechanicals (31 items), undated (Box 24:758)
    - Book (incomplete), 1976 (Box 24:759)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 24:760)
    - Scratchboard illustrations (2 items), 1975 (Box 39:1211)
  - Monticello, 1988
    - Manuscript draft #1 of 5, 1987 (Box 25:761)
    - Manuscript draft #2 of 5, 1987 (Box 25:762)
    - Manuscript draft #3 of 5, 1987 (Box 25:763)
    - Manuscript draft #4 of 5, 1987 (Box 25:764)
    - Manuscript draft #5 of 5, 1987 (Box 25:765)
    - Picture captions, undated (Box 25:766)
    - Flap text, undated (Box 25:767)
    - Galley #1 of 2, 1987 August 27 (Box 25:768)
    - Galley #2 of 2, 1987 October 1 (Box 25:769)
    - Dummy, 1988 (Box 25:770)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 25:771)
  - On the Wings of Peace, 1995
    - "Off to War" manuscript, 1994 (Box 25:772)
    - "Troopship" manuscript, 1994 (Box 25:773)
    - Book lay-out / dimensions, 1994 (Box 25:774)
    - Photocopies of articles on subject from publisher, 1985-1994 (Box 25:775)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 25:776)
  - Soldier Boy, Soldier Boy [Unpublished]
    - "Troopship" manuscript, undated (Box 25:777)
    - "The Spartans" manuscript, undated (Box 25:778)
    - "Off to War" manuscript, undated (Box 25:779)
    - "The Hindenberg" manuscript, undated (Box 25:780)
    - Complete manuscript, undated (Box 25:781)
  - The Jetty Chronicles, 1997
    - Manuscript, undated (Box 25:782)
    - Manuscript, 1993 (Box 25:782A)
    - Manuscript- edited and signed, 1997 (Box 25:782B)
    - Faxed cover and flap text, 1997 February 27 (Box 25:782C)
  - Letters From Italy, 1977
    - Notes, undated (Box 26:783)
    - Page drafts (incomplete), undated (Box 26:784)
    - Manuscript draft, 1976 (Box 26:785)
    - Manuscript- Part II, undated (Box 26:786)